Anna Rusyayeva

Email: annarsve@gmail.com Mobile: +7(922)159-60-30

Github: https://github.com/VanillaWulf

Linkedin: https://www.linkedin.com/in/anna-rusyaeva-6b1276148

SUMMARY

Five years of experience in commercial development for varying business areas provided me with the skill to understand client's goals and to create tasks to achieve it. Thanks to a solid set of marketing tools, I promote the relevant customers in the right direction according to the needed intention. Moreover, with the help of excellent building communications with current teams and contractors, I clearly plan tasks and hand over projects on time.

SKILLS

- Agile (SCRUM, Kanban, scrumban)
- Managing projects (Trello, Jira)
- **E-commerce** (Yandex Direct, Yandex Metrics, Google AdWords, Google Analytics)
- Market research
- Marketing (POSM, presentations, mailings)
- Sales analytics
- User demand analysis
- Developing cases for new products/features (IDEF, UML)
- **Design** (sketch, mogups, figma, adobe products)
- Strong technical stack (HTML, CSS, JS, ReactJS, Angular, git)

WORK EXPERIENCE

Freelancer September 2018

- Mobile app development
- Websites development
- Payment system development

Senior Marketing Manager - 000

October 2017 - June 2018

'Ideco'

- Project management (launch, maintaining and updating)
- Development process management (technical specifications for designers and developers)
- Organisation Agile workflow (Jira, Trello)
- · Planning budgets
- Creating roadmaps
- SMM

'Index Art'

- POSM
- Sales analytics
- Making bases for cold calling
- Quarterly reports about efficiency of marketing activities

SEO Specialist - Advertising Agency January 2017 - October 2017



PROJECTS



Development + marketing strategy

Landing Page



Development + marketing strategy

Catalog of

projects



Web catalog development based on printed one

<u>Domain</u> relocation



Domain relocation without organic traffic loses

- Technical auditing (layout, structure, accessibility)
- Task management Technical auditing (developers, designers, writers)
- Creation and testing of hypotheses for increasing traffic (ui/ux, structure, HTML, core, content)
- Attendance and behavior analytics
- Creating monthly reports for customers

Context Advertising and SEO Specialist -

December 2015 - September 2016

Advertising Agency 'ManyLetters'

- Creating and running campaigns in Yandex. Direct, Google AdWords, MvTarget
- Coordination updates with clients
- Writing specifications for programmers
- Creating monthly reports for customers

Software Engineer -

October 2013 - September

Special design bureau 'Peleng'

- Writing technical specification for software
- Detecting of software functionality flaws
- Revising software in C++
- Modular and integration testing

2014



App for iOS & Android

EDUCATION

Beijing University of Aeronautics and Astronautics February 2015 Master of Computer Science

Ural Federal University

2015

Master of Computer Science in Technology in Mathematical Software and Information Systems Administration

Ural Federal University

2013

Higher Professional Education in Legal Regulation of Business

Ural Federal University

2013

Bachelor of Computer Science in Technology in Design and Technology of Electronic Means

LANGUAGES

App for shools

Russian native speaker English - B2

Website НОЧЛЕЖКА

Design + development.



company.

